

Q Radovanje 63, Slavonski Brod, 35250, Croatia

+385996816422

Profile

I am an experienced Frontend Developer with a solid grasp of core web technologies (HTML, CSS, and JavaScript).

Thanks to this, I've expanded my knowledge further into bleeding-edge technologies like React, TypeScript, CSS Preprocessors (SASS), and Component Libraries (MUI).

Employment History

Frontend Developer, Q agency, Zagreb

November 2021 - Present

- -executing responsive design while developing interactive SPAs and websites
- -analyzing and improving UI/UX systems
- -researching, documenting and improving APIs
- -holding demos and presentations to clients

Junior Full Stack Developer, BESOFT, Rijeka

May 2021 — October 2021

- -designing and developing responsive and interactive single and multi-page applications client side
- -designing RESTful APIs, developing a server, and integrating the frontend with the backend
- -database modeling

Frontend Developer, Freelancer, Slavonski Brod

February 2021 — April 2021

- -developing responsive static websites for small businesses and marketing purposes
- -hosting and maintaining websites
- -consulting website owners on UI/UX and performance improvements

English and German teacher, Primary School Sibinj, Sibinj

2019 — 2021

- -Creating lesson plans, educational materials and tests
- -Holding lectures
- -Explaining and analyzing educational content

Education

Master's degree in teaching English and German language and literature, University Josip Juraj Strossmayer, Osijek

2011 - 2017

| \mathbf{r} | -4- | .:1 | _ |
|--------------|-----|-----|---|
| υ | eta | Ш | s |

Nationality

Croatian

Driving license

B2

Date / Place of birth

27.04.1992.

Slavonski Brod

Links

Personal website

LinkedIn

GitHub

Skills

HTML5

CSS3

Sass

JavaScript

React

TypeScript

MUI

iQuery

Node.js

Git

Languages

Croatian

English

German